proshares.com 2019-07-13

# Notice of Privacy Policy

**ProFunds, Access One Trust, ProFund Advisors LLC, ProShares, ProShare Advisors LLC and ProShare Capital Management LLC**

## Our commitment to you

ProFunds, Access One Trust, ProFund Advisors LLC, ProShares Trust, ProShares Trust II, ProShare Advisors LLC and ProShare Capital Management LLC ("The Funds") are committed to respecting the privacy of personal information you entrust to us in the course of doing business.

## The information we collect about you

The Funds collect non-public personal information from various sources. For instance, account applications may include name, address, and social security number. The Funds receive information from transactions in your accounts, including account balances, and from correspondence between you and the Funds or third parties, such as the Fund's service providers. The Funds use such information provided by you or your representative to process transactions, to respond to inquiries from you, to deliver reports, products, and services, and to fulfill legal and regulatory requirements.

In addition, our website uses "cookies" and other similar technology to help us measure and track visitors to the website and to collect certain technical and navigational information, such as browser type, internet protocol address, pages visited and time on site. This information may be used to help us serve you better by improving website design and functionality, and it may be used to help us provide customized services and information to you (e.g., we may use information about your visits to help target advertisements for products and services available from the Funds). The use of cookies and like technologies is common practice on the internet and many browsers are initially configured to accept cookies automatically. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, notify you when a cookie is set, or delete cookies that have already been set. Each browser is different, so check your browser's "help" menu, refer to its instruction documentation, or seek online assistance to learn how to change your browser preferences.

We may also use third party advertising companies (e.g., Google) to serve online ads for The Funds to you on our behalf based on your visits to our and other websites. These ads may appear on a wide variety of websites, which have no affiliation with The Funds. We neither collect nor share any personally identifiable information with these advertising companies or websites and they neither collect nor share personally identifiable information with The Funds. Third party advertising companies may use cookies and other similar technologies to measure and improve the effectiveness of advertising for their clients, including The Funds. To do so, these companies may collect and use limited technical and other anonymous information about your browsing activity, potentially including: date/time the ad is shown, cookies, IP address information, browser and device information, etc. You may opt-out of receiving third-party served advertisements by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads) and by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## How we handle your personal information

The Funds do not disclose any non-public personal information about their customers to anyone unless permitted by law or approved by the customer. The Funds may share information with certain third parties who are not affiliated with ProFunds to process or service a transaction at your request or as permitted by law. For example, sharing information with non-affiliated third parties that maintain or service customer accounts for the Funds is essential. The Funds may also share information with companies that perform administrative or marketing services for the Funds including research firms. When the Funds enter into such a relationship, such third parties' use of customers' information is restricted and they are prohibited from sharing it or using it for any purposes other than those for which they were hired. The Funds also require service providers to maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard non-public personal information of customers of the Funds.

## How we safeguard your personal information

The Funds maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect your personal information. Within the Funds, access to personal information is restricted to those employees who require access to that information in order to provide products or services to our customers such as processing transactions and handling inquiries. The Fund's employment policies restrict the use of customer information and require that it be held in strict confidence.

The Funds will adhere to the policies and practices described in this notice for both current and former customers of the Funds.

_This Privacy Policy applies to the ProFunds family of funds, Access One Trust family of funds, ProFund Advisors LLC, ProShares Trust family of funds, ProShares Trust II family of funds, ProShare Advisors LLC and ProShare Capital Management LLC._
